In the year 199X...
The Earth was engulfed
in nuclear flames.
FIST OF THE NORTH STAR
You're in shock!
The sky's falling down with love
It's falling down on my chest
Even if he binds my burning heart
with chains, now it's useless...
I'll down the bastard who gets
in my way with just one fingertip!
You're in shock!
Heartbeats rise with love
My heartbeat rises
My heart, wandering in search
of you, now burns passionately...
It will melt everything
and splash against the cruelty!
To protect your love with me,
you set off on a journey
And lost sight of tomorrow
I never want to see that your
face has forgotten how to smile
Take back the love!
The oceans have dried up.
The land has been torn apart.
It is a world in which no
living thing seems to be left.
However, mankind hasn't died.
- Zeed!
- Zeed's coming!
Go faster!
No good!
This is as fast as it'll go!
- They've even got clothes!
- This cow looks delicious!
They carried this crap, too?
Not like it's worth anything anymore.
No kidding!
Can't even blow your nose with it.
Nuclear war has destroyed
all of human civilization.
The world has been plunged into...
an age of chaos and
terror ruled by violence.
Yuria.
Yuria...
Zeed! We've got trouble!
- Our scouts! Somebody's...!
- What?
Who?! Who did this?!
They did this knowing
they were Zeed gang members?!
Hey, Zeed!
There's something weird
about these bodies.
I've never seen wounds like this.
It's almost like they were
ripped apart from the inside.
Zeed!
This one's still breathing!
What?
Hey! What was it?
What happened?!
H-H-Hokuto--!
"Hokuto"?
What's going on?
It's like he had a
mini timebomb in him!
No. A weapon that sophisticated
shouldn't exist anymore.
Who did this?
What did he mean by "Hokuto"?
Oh, it's you.
Forget it, Lin. We don't have
any water to give your dog.
For crying out loud...
Okay,just a little.
Hey! You damned thief!
God dammit! You, again?!
You... Trying to steal
our potatoes again!
That's the fourth time!
We're gonna hang you, Bat.
H- Hang me?!
You just go ahead and try!
I'll come back
and haunt your ass!
Oh, this kid's hopeless!
Lock him up!
Hey! We've got another one!
Over here!
Great, a water thief now?
- Now's my chance...
- Hey!
W- Water...
Lin, keep an eye on them.
Idiot! You really screwed up.
Th- Thank you...
Hurry up! Get the key!
What're you waiting for?!
They'll hang us both!
You were caught stealing, too,
you know!
That hurts! What'd you do?!
Forgive me. May I have
another cup of water?
Ow... What the
hell's your problem?
What happens to that girl
watching us if you run away?
Hah! That's a wimpy thing
to say in this day and age!
How'd you ever manage
to live this long?
What, you brought food, too?
Thanks.
I feel much better now.
But won't you get
in trouble for this?
Oh, isn't that cute?
She's blushing!
My name's Kenshiro,
but you can call me Ken.
What's your name?
Forget it. She doesn't talk.
Her heart's closed up.
She doesn't talk?
Yeah.
It's not surprising, really.
She saw her parents and brother get
killed by bandits before her eyes.
Papa!
Mama!
Lin's family was
killed before her eyes.
Ever since then, the shock
has kept her from talking.
She has no one now.
That's why she has to
stand guard in the jail...
even though she's
just a little kid.
These villagers are really
pretty mean to her.
Sucks to be a
little kid nowadays.
Guess she chose the
wrong time to be born.
Hey, I'm sorry!
Don't look at me like that.
I'm sorry...
It's tough, huh?
Her young eyes must
have seen such hell...
It's all right.
Please hold still.
Wha...
Hey, what're you doing?!
Just a little magic spell.
To let her talk.
Oh, please!
You gotta be kidding!
The rest is up to her heart.
Her heart's cries will summon words.
Out! The elder's back.
Where are you going?
Nowhere special.
Elder, you think he might
be one of Zeed's men?
If he is, then he'll carry the
mark somewhere on his body.
Check him out.
Elder! What's wrong?!
The mark of the Big Dipper!
The stars which foretell death!
Where they appear,
chaos follows!
This is a bad omen!
Trouble!
It's Zeed! Zeed's gang!
Come on, Lin.
You have to fight, too.
Oh, man!
She's got it bad for you!
She left you the keys because
she knows she'll get killed.
- Get killed?
- Yeah, they're fighting Zeed.
They kill everyone.
Women, children, whoever.
Darn it,
what's with this thing?!
Uh, h- hey!
Where are you going?
We'll just get killed
if we mess with Zeed!
We've gotta get outta here!
They're gonna kill us, too!
Don't try to fight us,
or I'll twist this girl's head off!
You got that?
Now bring us all your food!
We've got no choice!
Let's fight them!
Guess you won't believe me
unless you see me do it!
KEN!!!
Stay back!
She... She talked!
Lin talked!
Who the hell is that guy?!
Who the hell are you?!
You bastard!
Get lost.
You've got some nerve!
You'll die for that!
Ken!
Why, you...
You won't make fools of us!
What the hell?!
What was that?!
What did he do?!
H-Hokuto Shinken!
Let that girl go now.
Was it you?!
You killed my men?
For that,
I'll twist this kid apart!
The Hundred Crack
Fist of the North Star!
I'd heard that, long ago, a terrible
killing technique came out of China.
Hokuto Shinken,
the Holy Fist of the North Star.
All of the practitioner's energy
is concentrated into one blow...
and it shocks the hidden
power points of the body.
He's just performed
a killing technique...
that ruptures the body from
within instead of from without!
Your fists are about as
strong as a mosquito's.
You are already dead.
What?
What is he?!
Behold, Yuria.
The shining city of
Southern Cross belongs to you.
Every blade of grass
and tree in it is yours.
Shin, you don't understand anything.
What I want is
gentleness like the sea.
Eyes that shine
like a green meadow.
A heart that's
warm like the sun.
Yuria!
Yuria, why won't you
open your heart to me?
Lord King.
Kenshiro still lives.
He was sighted by
someone in the desert.
Damn his persistence!
But he'll never make it here.
Kenshiro, look and see what...
I have wrought upon the land
while you were wandering in hell!
With a single word from me, thousands
of mighty men will attack you!
Your body will turn to dust
in the desert...
and your soul
will wander in darkness!
Just watch, Kenshiro.
See my power!
Colonel!
This is a search order from God!
He is Kenshiro, the man
with seven scars on his chest...
and successor to the
knowledge of Hokuto Shinken!
Kill him!
Leave this to me, Colonel.
I have no use for sheep!
Come out, Hokuto Man!
Here I am,
soldiers of the false god.
I admire your courage...
seeing how you came out here
yourself to be killed!
You are the ones who will die!
It's been a while since I've
fought a man with spirit like you!
And I'm the last man you'll ever meet
before you go to hell!
This isn't an
ordinary whip I have.
Its cut is far sharper than a knife's.
Come and get me!
The moment you charge,
I'll slice your body in two!
Well, what's wrong?!
Come and get me!
North Star
Muscle Control Spin Kick!
Im- Impossible!
How could he be so fast?!
I-- I can't move!
So, how does it feel
as you approach your execution?
What?
Muscle Control Spin Kick...
is one of the secret techniques
of Hokuto Shinken.
I've upset your body's workings
so I can make you do what I want.
Wha- What the...?
What are you...?!
I just pressed Meiken, one of
your body's hidden power points.
Your arms will keep moving apart
until you strangle yourself.
You belong in hell.
W-W-Wait!
I don't want to die!
Help me!
These are terrible times...
So, you've made it this far,
Man With Seven Scars.
Are you the colonel?
The one and only!
And that man there
is OUR god. Observe!
We are one with our god...
and from Him we have
received a commandment.
A commandment to kill you,
Man With Seven Scars!
Die, mouse who dares to defy God!
- How...?
- I'm a telepath.
I can predict every move
you plan to make.
No matter what you try...
my boomerangs will
cut into your flesh.
Let's go!
Extreme Air Current Dance!
The Hokuto Shinken
I study how the air flows
and follow its movements.
You can't attack me
from any direction now!
So, that was the legendary
martial art, Hokuto Shinken, eh?
I've mastered every form
of killing art there is...
and the Chinese martial arts
are my specialty.
You must know of it as well.
The most powerful killing
technique in the world.
The Silent Fist of the South Star!
You won't even be able to
touch my body.
I'll simply slash you to death!
I know every move
you're going to make!
Now, where should I hit next?
What's that?
You're able to
predict my movements...
by seeing where I'm looking and by
the subtle movements of my muscles.
However, if I suppress
all of my body's aura...
you won't be able to predict
what I'll do!
Then I'll suppress my aura as well.
How will you fight
if you can't guess my movements?
Now you're nothing
but a statue!
The Hundred Crack
Fist of the North Star!
This is impossible!
You managed to touch my body!
All you do is
mimic the martial arts.
But I'm a professional who
has been trained since birth.
The blood and technique
of the 2000-year-old art...
of Hokuto Shinken
flows through my body.
Ken!
Ken, I'll help you fight!
Stay back, Lin!
God has not abandoned me!
Ken...
K- Ken...
You fool!
Because of one little girl...
your amazing power
has vanished, hasn't it?
Ken...
I'm all right.
You can't fight with
a wound like that!
Let's go!
My eyes... My eyes!
MY EYES!!!
My eyes!
I have already pressed Doumei,
one of your hidden power points.
Now you'll have your turn
to fear the darkness.
There will be no light for you
tomorrow!
The Bone Breaking Punch
of the North Star!
You are already dead.
Why? With your power,
you can have anything!
Do whatever you want!
You could be God Himself!
And yet you...!
You'll... You'll regret this!
Ken!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Not good enough!
What are you doing out there?!
Y- Yes, sir..!
I won't allow him
to enter this city!
Gather the army at once!
We'll put together
all our forces and then kill him!
I want him buried in the
deepest pit of hell!
Y- Yes, sir!
Yuria... What I want
most is your heart.
And to do that, I swear...
I swear that Kenshiro...
will die!
Hey! Start it!
Where is he?!
Up there!
If that guy's after you...
all that's waiting for you
is 100% certain death!
There's only one way
we'll save ourselves!
Shit...
Wh- What are you...?
We're taking your head!
If we give your head to
the man with seven scars...
he might let us live!
Wh- What did you say?!
You make a speciality of
screwing over your friends.
Well, now it's your turn!
What are you talking about, guys?
You know what's going on, right?
He wants to hunt us ALL down!
Then it's better to have him
just hunting YOU down!
Get some!
Stupid idiots...
Hm? Who are you?!
Jackal! At last I have you!
It's you! W- Wait a sec!
I finally found you!
I wanted to apologize!
C'mon, can't we be friends?
C'mon, forgive me, please.
- Die!
- You reveal your true nature, villain!
This guy ain't human!
He's a monster!
A devil to kill another devil...
I hear it. I hear it!
The devil's roar...
Soon, now...
You'll be out of there soon.
Now, awaken at last,
Devil Reverse!
Murderer of 700 people!
Sent to be executed 13 times!
And yet you survived
every attempt!
The personification of Satan!
DEVIL REVERSE!
You've come!
The man with seven scars!
It was you?!
Were you the one who
locked me in here?!
Devil! Kill him!
Kill...!
That's the way,
Devil Reverse! Get him!
His speed!
The way he carries himself!
What is this guy?!
You fool!
You thought Devil Reverse...
only had brute strength
and bulk going for him?!
This is... The Arhat Deva Fist!
The Arhat Deva Fist!
The Arhat Deva Fist is
a deadly martial art...
whose history goes
back 5000 years to India.
Having nearly
unlimited destructive power...
the utter fierceness of this
killing technique was such that...
the master of time decreed that
it was forbidden...
and it was said the
technique was never passed on.
He couldn't have killed 700 people
with just his incredible strength!
Devil Reverse earned the name of
the personification of Satan...
by being the inheritor
of the Arhat Deva Fist!
Your end is near!
Very well! If the Arhat Deva Fist
is the personification of the devil...
then I'll show you
how Hokuto Shinken...
is the personification of
Indra, the god of battle!
Wh- What the...?!
Secret Hokuto Shinken technique!
The Spinning Dragon
Breathing Technique!
Devil! Show him the secrets
of the Arhat Deva Fist!
Devil can freely control the wind!
There's nowhere you can run!
Death Wind Golden Steel Fist!
It worked!
You fool! Now the man I hate most
has been buried for good!
Now I don't have to
bow before King!
I'm the master of the world!
Im- Impossible!
There's no way he could have survived
hitting the wall that hard!
The secret of the breathing technique
lies in changing silence to action!
And... Those who witness
this technque must die!
D- Devil! Kill him!
Smash him to death!
Devil! Don't let him
touch your body!
That's right! Crush him!
The North Star
Seven Star Points of Death!
Devil...
Thanks to using
the breathing technique...
I've struck seven of his hidden
power points with all my strength.
Death is his only fate now.
Sleep, demons...
Ken, neither you
nor Saki are here with me...
I'm all alone now...
Yuria, I'm here with you.
Shin...
Yuria...!
Why, Yuria?
Shin, you just don't understand.
You're a warrior.
I know you can
build a huge empire.
But what I want is
kindness as vast as the sea.
A heart that's warm like the sun.
The shine of a wind blown
through a meadow...
Yuria...
It's burning...
The city of Southern Cross...!
Burning... The city is burning.
Everything I've worked for is lost!
Shin's army is destroyed...
and looters have
set the city ablaze.
Southern Cross,
once a city of prosperity...
is now covered by
the shadow of death.
And the star of destiny
leads Kenshiro and Shin...
closer and closer to their
fated final confrontation!
Shin! I finally have you!
It's the man with seven scars!
The man with seven scars is here!
It's him!
The man with seven scars!
The man with seven scars
is still alive!
What?
I see. The man with
seven scars is still alive.
Kenshiro still lives!
We are Lord King's
personal bodyguards!
We won't let you pass!
North Star Whirlwind Group Attack
Shin! I came back from the depths
of hell to get to you again!
Kenshiro...
It's been a long time.
Where's Yuria?!
Why don't you come
and see for yourself?
Yuria...!
Yuria has already said
she's forgotten about you.
In exchange for your life.
It was Yuria who saved you
when I gave you those seven scars.
Ken!
There's a very definite
difference between you and me.
Ambition.
You have no ambition.
Ambition is what gives you power.
Yuria, say that you love me.
No! If you kill Ken,
I'll die too!
Oh...?
How many can Ken take
before he dies?
Yuria, live!
You have to live on!
Ken...
Now die!
Wait!
Yuria, don't do it!
I... I'll love you...
What?! I can't hear you!
Yuria!
I'll love you, Shin!
I'll follow you forever!
Yuria...!
Ken!
Yuria!!!
It doesn't matter
that she's forgotten me.
As long as she's still alive...
Kenshiro!
I've already beaten you!
Try again and again and
the result will be the same.
But it will be amusing
to cut you to ribbons...
in front of
the woman you love!
You've gotten good at dodging.
But you can never
follow the moves I make!
Kenshiro! I'll send you
back down to hell!
South Star Thousand Dragon Head Attack!
Wh- What...?!
You... You really aren't
the man I once knew! Why...?!
Obsession...
The obsession you taught me!
You are no match
for me now. Give up.
Your obsession is nothing to me!
Shin, I can follow
every move you make.
You can't win.
Never underestimate me!
Hell's Death Fist of the South Star!
Flying Defensive Fist of the North Star!
Im... Impossible!
Don't worry.
I didn't hit a power point.
Even if they approached me
without a single sound...
no one can sneak up on me.
Will you give Yuria back?
You've shown me
how obsessed you really are.
Then why don't I destroy the
object of your obsession?!
Yuria!
Yuria... Even in death,
your face is beautiful.
Y-Y-Yuria...!
Now, even if you kill me,
Yuria is dead!
Half of your obsession
is now gone!
K- Kenshiro...
Shin... You're a dead man!
Die!!!
North Star Cross Slash!
Why...?
What allowed me to
counter your technique...
was rage!
A rage even stronger
than my obsession!
Rage...
How long until I die?
I've struck power points on you
in the shape of a bloody cross.
You will die admiring
your own emblem.
In three minutes...
Y- Yuria!
This is...!
Yes. Our battle...
is not yet over...
This is a doll!
What's the meaning of this?!
Shin!
Dead... Yuria is dead...
And now no one can ever end this
battle between the two of us...
Southern Cross is burning.
Your city is burning.
The grass, the trees,
the people in it...
They all belonged to you.
But don't worry, Yuria.
We can build a new one.
A city even larger and more
glorious than Southern Cross.
And more suitable
for you as its queen.
I can do it
as long as you're with me!
You're going to do
the same thing again?
Even worse than
you did before...
As long as my feelings
for you don't change...
you'll keep on doing this,
won't you?
Even more innocent
people will die.
I can't take it anymore!
Y- Yuria! What are you...?!
Ken... I couldn't
keep my promise to you!
It can't ...
Why? Why?! WHY?!
Yuria!!!
And I cried. For the first
time in my life, I cried.
In the end, I could
never possess her heart.
Because always in her heart...
was you.
This city... Southern Cross,
which I built for Yuria...
Southern Cross, which has
now fallen to ashes...
It is her gravestone now.
Behold! Yuria's gravestone!
The city of Southern Cross...
But this city... All the power
and wealth I've amassed...
It's all empty, in the end.
I only wanted one thing!
Yuria!!!
It looks like this is it for me...
But I refuse to die
by your technique!
Kenshiro...
Farewell!!!
Shin!
They live within time
The lonely whispers
While fumbling, I recall
The warmth and lonesomeness
Sparkling dazzingly
I embrace your body now
Yes, to the person I love,
time drifts away
To the wandering heart,
tomorrow is invisible
Ken!!!
Ken, it's over, isn't it?
You did it, Ken!
But why, Ken?! Why make a
grave for a guy like that?!
Because he loved
the woman I loved.
Chapter 1: END
Farewell... My friend.