One man carves out
his own destiny!
One man defies the heavens!
That is the 2,000 year destiny of
the Divine Fist of the North Star.
Behold!
That long, bloody history
will now come to an end!
LEGEND OF THE SAVIOR
OF THE CENTURY'S END
FIST OF THE NORTH STAR
You cannot love with a cool heart
Even if you tire of waiting
the dawn will never come
He stands alone...
He searches for his
dreams in the flames...
That sway in darkness
The thristy heart...
Searches and cries
Unable to see tomorrow...
At the edge of this never-ending journey!
I am Ken-Oh,
the ruler of the century's end!
Raoh...
[ narration ]
The Five Chariot Stars protect
the polar star of the South Star.
Kaze, kumo, honou, yama, umi...
They are... The Wind.
The Clouds.
The Flames.
The Mountains.
The Ocean.
So that the last general of
the South Star Six Sacred Fists
may shine eternally...
We, the Five Chariot Stars,
dance throughout the heavens...
And run across the land.
For that purpose, we would all
gladly be crushed into pieces.
The last general of the
South Star awaits you.
Why would the last general
of the South Star want me?
The North Star and the South Star
are two sides of the same coin.
When the two unite,
this chaotic world will be at peace.
Our general has chosen you over
Ken-Oh as the North Star.
The savior of the century's end,
rather than the ruler of it.
But I am no savior.
I just want to seal Raoh's...
No, Ken-Oh's fists...
For breaking the code
of the North Star.
Let's go.
- Hold on, Ken!
- One moment, please.
You must meet the last
general of the South Star.
That is your destiny!
My destiny, you say?
I cannot speak
any further for yet...
But please trust me,
Fudo of the Mountains,
and come to the capital of the
South Star to meet our general!
Fudo, I'll trust the light
in your eyes.
Then...
Let's go to the capital
of the South Star.
Right!
[ narration ]
We've completely concealed our
general's identity until now.
There's only one reason for that...
To keep it from reaching the ears
of the terrifying ruler of
the century's end, Ken-Oh.
If he ever knew, Raoh would
ruthlessly rush to the capital.
Our general is a woman.
A... woman?
Did you say, woman?
Indeed. The last general of the
South Star Six Sacred Fists is...
That woman is...
...the woman you loved,
Yuria-sama!
Yu... Yuria?
Kenshiro.
Yuria!
Kenshiro! Yuria is mine!
Raoh.
If the last general of the
South Star is Yuria!
She's the only woman worthy
of me, the King of Fists.
I will conquer the South Star,
and have Yuria kneel before me.
Raoh!
[ narration ]
Damn you!
North Star Iron Palm Wave!
This is...
Rei's style!
But his body was
shattered twice!
And yet, did his body just
vanish into thin air?
What sorrowful eyes!
Could this be the ultimate
secret technique of
the Divine Fist of the North Star
Ryuken told me about...
Unconscious Transmigration?
My master, Ryuken.
Let me ask you one last thing!
I've heard the Divine Fist
of the North Star...
...has an ultimate secret technique
called Unconscious Transmigration.
What sort of secret
technique is it?
Even I cannot teach it.
In the 2,000 year history of the
Divine Fist of the North Star,
no one has ever mastered it!
What?
The strongest power in this
world is emptiness.
To rise from the emptiness
and still find life...
That is Unconscious Transmigration.
No matter how great
you become,
you will never master
that secret technique.
Do you understand, Raoh?
The greatness of your
ambition will keep you
from ever knowing sadness.
Only those who bear sadness
can accomplish it.
Sadness...
Only those who bear sadness
can accomplish it.
Sadness...
So have you become
the strongest man
in the 2,000 year history of
the Divine Fist of the North Star,
by bearing sadness?
All of you!
I can see it!
The blood shed by
those chosen men
flows within Kenshiro-sama!
Raoh... Toki is waiting.
It's useless.
Raoh, that's enough.
I am Ken-Oh...
I can never be defeated!
What's this... Raoh has
thrown away his life!
For the first time
he is prepared for death,
and is aiming for
a mutual death!
Gouge my eyes out...
Crush my hands, Kenshiro!
Even if you can,
you shall see death!
Th... this is...
Raoh...
Kenshiro,
it has come to an end...
Farewell, Raoh.
Die, Kenshiro!
Damn it! The final mechanism
has been set off!
Kenshiro-sama, get down!
Damn you, Rihaku...
I was just one step away
from defeating Kenshiro...
Yu... Yuria!
Ra... Raoh...
Luck is on my side!
The heavens have
chosen Raoh after all!
- Raoh!
- You will not have Yuria-sama!
Get lost!
Yuria!
[ narration ]
Yuria-sama!
- Yuria-sama!
Even blazing flames cannot
burn this perfected body.
My flesh is undefeatable!
And yet, I felt fear.
I was shaken by Kenshiro's eyes...
Now that I've felt fear, I can no
longer call myself the King of Fists.
Kenshiro. What made
me fear was... sorrow.
Kenshiro's love for Yuria.
Does grief surpass the body?
Is grief... love?
You're crying...
The heavens that lost the
Five Chariot Stars is grieving.
Raoh...
Yuria... Give me your life!
- My life?
- Yes... I must take your life!
I have only Kenshiro
in my mind...
My skills, body, and spiritual
energy all surpass Kenshiro's.
But I still understand
neither sadness, nor love...
I've heard love brings sadness,
and that sadness brings love!
I may come to understand
all of it... if I lose you.
Raoh...
Yuria... prepare yourself!
You curs...
You can't, Ken-Oh-sama.
You cannot lay a hand on her!
I beg of you!
Take our lives instead!
Please, do not harm the lady!
- I beg of you!
- As do I!
You have all been struck by the
light of Yuria's motherly star?
- Ken-Oh-sama!
No, I refuse!
Yuria, I don't care
if you despise me!
What are you doing!
If you worry about your wound,
you cannot fight to full extent.
I don't need pity.
Before a fierce battle among men,
all I can do is see them off
as best as I can.
It must be hard to strike
while I'm looking at you...
I shall return to
heaven as well.
Are you throwing away your life?
For a new light.
I can see it...
the era of a new light.
The green trees.
The flowing streams.
The scent of the flowers.
The richness of the land,
and the aroma of the soil.
For the era of a new light,
fate cannot avoid the fight
between you and Kenshiro.
For that, I will give you
my life if necessary.
What is this intense feeling?
I must not falter!
What is this emotion!?
Did you understand, Raoh?
Toki...
What?
Te... Tears!?
L... Love?
You say this is love, Toki?
Have I been after
Yuria out of love!?
Right now... I can't have both
Yuria and Kenshiro.
Raoh... I mean, Ken-Oh,
has only one path to live.
Forgive me, Yuria!
Live on as sadness
within my heart, Yuria!
Ken-Oh-sama!
It is over...
- That's...
- No way! Ko... Koku-Oh!
Why is Koku-Oh here?
Raoh is calling.
Ken.
- Ken!
- He didn't call us...
The two will conclude their battle.
Kenshiro-san, leave
everything else to me.
Take care of them.
Ken... Please don't die.
I will protect the code
of the North Star.
Ken!
Don't die!
Raoh, wait for me!
Raoh!
The North Star Mind and Body
Training Ground.
In the 2,000 year history
of the North Star,
it is the most sacred of all
training grounds.
The battles for succession
have always been fought here.
Raoh.
Kenshiro.
To bury your bones, and the 2,000
year history of the North Star,
there is no better place.
Raoh, your ambition and your
fists will now come to an end.
I don't care about
the heavens any more!
No... the heaven I sought
may have been you!
Kenshiro!
The one to slaughter the greatest
North Star master will be Raoh.
That will begin a new history
for true, ultimate strength.
You'll die, not me.
Raoh, you are the only man to
break the code of the North Star...
As the true successor to the
Divine Fist of the North Star,
I must make you pay.
Kenshiro!
I'll smash you into dust!
Unconscious Transmigration...
A legendary secret technique
of the North Star,
mastered only by those
who bear true grief!
Before this ultimate technique,
Unconscious Transmigration...
Only death awaits.
The finishing strike!
Raoh?
You've mastered Unconscious
Transmigration as well?
I, too, had my heart steeped
in blood and filled with grief.
What?
Over there!
- Ken!
- Hey!
Yuria...
Yuria-san?
Raoh, what did you do to Yuria...
See it for yourself.
Yuria...
The first woman I ever
put my hands on...
But it was her life that fuelled my
Unconscious Transmigration.
Yuria-san...
Die!
They're fighting without
trying to block each other.
Strange... neither of them
are showing signs of hatred!
No, it's more like they're
becoming transparent...
I can see them,
back when they were little!
Huh?
Thinking back...
This is also where
we first met Yuria.
Brother...
If this keeps up,
they'll both die!
Ken...
You entered my...
fighting spiritual energy!
Ken's not even looking at Raoh,
just his spiritual energy!
He's assaulting
his foe's aura,
and unleashing an unconscious
attack into the confusion.
The next blow will mark
our last farewell.
Toki and I both idolized you,
Raoh, the great eldest
brother of the North Star!
That feeling is as strong as ever,
burned into my heart.
Ken-Oh-sama's energy is receding!
The maligned fighting spiritual
energy leaves him wide open.
Kenshiro's unconscious fist
won't miss a single opening...
Yuria-san, look...
Ken is fighting together
with Yuria-san's heart.
It'll soon come.
Their long lasting battles...
...will soon end.
And peace will come...
...to both of their souls...
Very well.
Try to take me down!
With the 2,000 year history
of the North Star...
I'll put my entire life
into these fists!
Take this fist
with all of my soul!
Raoh's aura is gone!
Perish in heaven, Kenshiro!
He did it!
That's impossible!
I am Raoh, and put all of
my soul into my fists!
Your heart stands alone.
But within my heart,
feelings for my brother Raoh...
and for Yuria, live on.
Even your hard fist style that
shattered heaven and earth...
cannot shatter these feelings.
Your strength comes from
differences between
one who abandoned love, and one
who embraced love into his heart?
Kenshiro!
Toki!
Raoh, it's alright to say it now.
Why don't you?
You haven't abandoned love.
Say that you have hid it
deep into your heart!
I won't!
I would rather die
than admit it!
Then will you accept the Death
Omen Star without saying anything?
What? The Death Omen Star?
Rihaku-sama,
the Death Omen Star!
Look how brightly the
Big Dipper shines now!
I see... so that's it.
So even the eyes of Rihaku
could not read Raoh...
His sorrowful heart.
Live on as sadness within
my heart, Yuria!
Forgive me!
Yuria! You are ill!
Just like Toki,
a fatal illness!
I have a few months left.
How long have you been...?
Soon after I was
taken away by Shin.
I was given a limited time to live.
So I thought I would live
as the heavens decreed,
without defiance.
When the general
of the South Star moves,
so does the North Star...
as do the heavens.
And such is the destiny of the
last general of the South Star.
So you chose for yourself,
to stay still and wait?
Even if it meant abandoning
your own happiness?
If my life can bring light
to this century's end...
Now, send me to heaven.
What a woman...
I cannot kill her!
I, Raoh, cannot cast
this woman away!
Yuria! I shall bear my
love for you forever!
Raoh must have struck a
pressure point on Yuria-sama,
and put her into a death-like
state to halt her illness.
By killing Yuria-sama...
he still couldn't obtain
Unconscious Transmigration.
But his love for Yuria-sama,
and his sorrow showed him.
But that's not enough...
This means Raoh also had
the right to be the successor
to the Divine Fist
of the North Star.
Ironically, the heavens sent
two successors to this world.
For Raoh, the eldest brother
of the North Star,
to bear love would be a disgrace!
If I did that, I would equal
Kenshiro in every way!
It's fine, brother.
The fight is over.
Unacceptable! I am the eldest
brother of the North Star!
I must die with my pride!
Damn you!
I shall show you...
how Raoh, the ruler of the
century's end, meets his end!
Kenshiro!
I, Raoh, am not dead yet!
Ken! Stop it!
Yuria-san?
I don't believe it!
Kenshiro!
You and I should be equal
in all respects now!
There is no way my fists
cannot take you down!
So you already knew?
My fists no longer have
the strength to take you on.
Raoh...
Now I understand!
You have lived all this time
by seeing through death!
Fighting alongside
irreplaceable friends...
you've seen the line
between life and death!
Friends...
Friends, huh?
Thinking back, the only man
I could call a friend was Toki.
Show me...
Show the face of the man
who has defeated Raoh.
Impressive, my little brother.
Brother!
Yuria-san! Yuria-san!
- Her eyes opened!
- Yuria-san!
Ken!
Yuria-san!
Yuria-san is alive!
What?
Go!
Ken...
Yuria...
It was so long...
So long...
But finally...
Ken...
Yuria!
Your life will be spared for
a few more years!
Spend those remaining years
with Kenshiro in peace,
and live happily!
Raoh...
Could you have given Yuria your
own fighting spiritual energy...?
Farewell, Kenshiro.
I shall return to heaven...
Where Toki awaits.
- Raoh!
- Stay back!
What are you gonna do for me?
Your eyes can only see Yuria!
And besides...
I, Raoh, need no one's help
to return to heaven!
- What's this?
- Raoh's body is turning white!
I have not a shred of
regret for my entire life!
Raoh...
The great star falls.
Behold... Light has returned
to this world.
If it weren't for Raoh,
Kenshiro and Yuria-sama...
this world would have been
in darkness forever.
- Light!
- There's light shining!
The light has returned!
- It's so warm!
- Alright!
This is the light of freedom!
- Yeah!
- Hooray!
- Here we go!
- Do it!
- Over here, over here!
- Hold it tight, now!
- Line up properly, now!
- There's plenty, don't worry!
Come on, wait up!
If Raoh hadn't given his fighting
spiritual energy to Yuria...
...I might have lost.
No!
Terror was the only way to
rule this violent wasteland.
But ruling by terror
doesn't bring true peace.
Raoh must have wished he'd
be defeated by one who loved.
He must have wished that,
one day, warm light will...
pour down onto this
wasteland once again.
I can't help but believe it.
Raoh...
You were my
greatest friend.
Raoh, rest in peace with Toki.
I shall hold your
life in my heart,
and live on as the successor to
the Divine Fist of the North Star!
- Ke... Ken!
- No, Bat!
We can't! We promised
we wouldn't follow them!
Please let them be alone!
Let them live quietly
by themselves!
Lin...
But I'm sure that Ken
will come back someday!
I know he will...
Ken!