NARRATION
FIST OF THE NORTH STAR
TV COMPILATION 2
Six Sacred Fists of Nanto!
Rei, the Star of Justice
Wait! Wait for us!
Hey, wait up! Come on, lady!
Let's have some fun!
Wait up, lady!
Whoa, she's a pretty one!
I'm gettin' excited already!
We've got a lot of food.
Play nice with us
and we'll give you some.
Really...
Then I'll just take it right now!
Y- You're a man?!
Whenever I disguise
myself as a woman...
perverts like you
inevitably show up.
But you people do
serve a purpose...
because you always
bring food to me!
Oh, gimme a break!
Who the hell are you?!
My name?
My name is Rei!
Rei of the Nanto Suichoken school!
Nanto Suichoken school?!
- Why, you...!
- Wait!
Too late...
It really is!
Nanto Suichoken!
The South Star Water Bird Fist!
Its movements are
supposedly as graceful...
as those of a bird
floating on the water!
However, its power and cruelty as
a killing technique are unmatched!
Oh...? You seem to know
a bit about it.
You have to be strong if you
expect to survive in this world!
No one has ever been able
to stand up to my nunchakus!
Then I'll be the first.
Like hell!
Take that! And that!
And that! And... huh?
You dropped these.
You cannot counter my movements.
Not there!
Do you know a man with
seven scars on his chest?!
N-N-N-NO!!!
I see... Then I have
no further use for you!
I'll take care of
that food you have.
Man With Seven Scars...
Until I kill you...
I'll even eat mud to survive!
This belongs to my little sister.
My sister Airi was to
wear this for her wedding.
And then, the night
before Airi's wedding...
Bandits attacked my village while
I was away. They killed my parents...
And took away Airi, who was
finally going to be happy!
Father!
Airi...!
I don't know what
the man looks like...
but with his last breath,
my father told me...
he had seven scars
on his chest.
Airi may already be dead...
But I don't think she is!
I can see her even now!
Her face stained with tears!
I can hear her calling
for me even now!
I swear I'll find the
man with seven scars...
And then kill him!
Airi, it's me! I've found you!
Who? Who is there?
A- Airi...
You're still alive, Airi!
Calm down, Rei!
Don't go any closer!
Let me go!
Rei! Calm down!
LET ME GO!!!
Airi! Look at this.
Try to remember!
It's the veil you were going to
wear for your wedding!
This embroidery...
Can it be...?
Big Brother?
Yes! Airi, it's me!
No... No...
I thought I'd never see
my brother again in this world.
If I knew I could, then I...
I never would have lost hope!
What...?
After it happened,
I had nothing left.
I was sold again and again
as a slave.
Despair... That's all I had left.
I didn't have the courage
to choose death.
So my only way to live in this world
was to close my mind to it.
What are you saying...?
Brother!
Big Brother, where are you?!
Come to me!
Airi!
- Big Brother!
- Airi!
Big Brother!
What are you...?!
GET OUT OF MY WAY!!!
Damn you...!
Big Brother!
AIRI!!!
Your dear sister
is now in my hands!
How dare you kill
my beloved sons...
S- Stop!
I want you all to
know the pain I feel!
Try it blindfolded now!
- Now with the other girl.
- Right.
Wait, please!
I'll do anything you say!
Just don't kill Airi!
In that case...
Kill the Hokuto man!
What?!
Calm down, Rei.
They're trying to kill
one of us first.
Don't let them get to you.
Think what would happen...
if the Nanto and Hokuto schools
fought each other!
What will you do, Nanto man?!
Rei...
Let's go, Ken!
Do it, Nanto man!
Destroy the follower of Hokuto!
Ken...
I just... I just don't
want to fight you.
But I have to kill you!
Rei! Unless you use all your skills,
you'll never kill me.
That stance... The legendary
North Star Ultimate Holy Ring!
You know what this
stance means, don't you?
What's up?
They ain't movin' at all!
You don't know just
how intense this battle is.
They're both guarding
themselves so carefully...
that neither one
of them can attack!
South Star Tiger Beating Dragon!
North Star Dragon Attacking Tiger!
Watch carefully. Those stances show
they're betting their lives on this.
The winner will be decided
in the next instant!
It's over!
As I thought...
We beat each other.
Ken! Rei!
They're both dead!
Kemada, Gibara...
My dear sons.
You have been avenged.
Serves you right!
We're leaving!
Now kill the women!
Stay back, you monsters!
What the hell...?!
Father!
Father, those guys...!
What about them?!
They're... They're...
They're...!
Ken!
Rei!
You tricked us!
Deceiving your
enemies to escape...
is also a technique
of our fighting styles.
The Ultimate Holy Ring
stance was a signal...
to attack each other's
power points to simulate death!
No fair!
You villains don't
deserve fair play!
You were in Death's grip
from the very start!
Mountain Splitting Wave!
The Fang Clan's been destroyed!
Now nobody will
threaten our village!
Light! Light has
returned to the village!
I guess this means
our job's finished.
What will you do now, Rei?
Find a nice, quiet
place to live with Airi.
I see.
Looks like I owe you
another big debt.
By the way, Rei...
are you going to stop looking
for the man with seven scars?
What?
You killed a lot of people
so you could kill him, right?
Th- This is...!
Ken, look!
Airi!
Big Brother!
Airi, you can...!
I can see. It's still a little fuzzy,
but I can see your face.
Ken...
- Big Brother!
- Airi!
All right!
Ken, even if you told me you were
the one who took Airi away...
I wouldn't believe it.
I know that much.
Hey, Mamiya, what's up?
What are you doing in a dress?
What?! You jerk.
NARRATION
We're under attack!
Ken-Oh's squad is attacking!
Ken-Oh's squad?
Airi-san!
Is that it?
There's still one runt left.
Lin!
Even children must swear
loyalty to Ken-Oh-sama.
Brand yourself with his crest.
If you don't want to, maybe
we'll have you dance on that...
until you're
burned to a crisp.
The choice is yours.
So, what will it be?
I won't do it!
I'll never obey devils like
you who prey on the weak!
What?
You've got guts,
you little brat!
I will not obey a demon.
Want a hand, little lady?
No need to be afraid!
Hey, who are you?
Rei!
What's with you, huh?
You're a demon in human guise!
What are you...
That's the South Star
Waterfowl Fist!
Rei!
Lin! Hang in there!
Hey! Who the hell are you?
Hey, say something!
You demons!
You'll pay!
You bastards...
You bastards!
The fire!
If my stomach
ignites, I'll blow up!
Help m...
How pathetic...
- Ken-Oh-sama!
This is Ken's older brother?
You must be Ken-Oh... no,
Kenshiro's older brother, Raoh.
So you're Rei.
It was a pleasure watching
your South Star Waterfowl Fist.
Then I'll show you the essence
of my techniques as well.
I'll ask you one thing.
Have you seen the star
adjacent to the Big Dipper?
I have.
Have you?
I see. Then you must have been
destined to fight against me.
Very well. Go ahead
and attack as you wish.
What? You won't dismount?
Do you think that I stand on
equal ground with you?
There is no man
left in this world...
who can force me
to stand on the ground.
Then you can die
together with your horse!
South Star Ultimate Technique
Self-Sacrifice
Counterbalance Fist!
Everyone, lend
me your strength!
He's going to try to
kill us both!
South Star Ultimate Technique
Self-Sacrifice
Counterbalance Fist!
Saw right through it.
You've seen the
Death Omen Star!
- Rei!
- Brother!
Rei!
Whoa, whoa, whoa there.
So you came, Kenshiro.
Raoh...
Ken!
Rei...
Kenshiro, it's a wonder
you've survived to this day...
with your naive
views on life.
For that, I praise you.
But those caught up
by passion will inevitably...
end up like this.
Rei!
- Rei!
- Brother!
Brother!
Why?
Why didn't you
wait for me?
Rei wanted to repay
his debt to you, Ken!
That's ridiculous.
Just for that?
Ken, stay away from him!
Ken!
Does this face look like it's
going to his death?
It'll be fine, Lin.
Right...
You look like you might
be stronger now.
But it seems like your naivety
has not changed at all.
Go ahead and try me.
I'll also ask you this.
Have you seen the star
adjacent to the Big Dipper?
No. What about it?
Then, that means it is not the
time for us to fight.
Where do you think your going? I'll
settle this with you right here.
Don't push your luck, Kenshiro.
This giant aura, it's much greater
than what Raoh used to have!
Very well. I'll grant your
wish and take you on.
Come, Kenshiro.
Show me how much you've grown!
You shall see it
through with death.
Ken!
I can see your fighting
spiritual energy clearly.
You've mastered it quite well...
What's happening?
The air...
The air is being
drawn towards them!
A tornado!
Ken!
Look, above us!
What a fool!
If this was night, you would
clearly see the Death Omen Star!
Learn how to fight off
of your damn horse!
North Star Seven
Deaths Cavalry Slash!
Ken!
You've scarred me.
I told you,
I'm not the man I once was.
Get off the horse.
You fool, you still don't
realize that your life was spared?
What?
That's...
This arrow.
If someone hadn't
hit me with this,
you'd be dead.
You over there, come out!
Rei, you...
Ken, just wait.
Rei!
- Brother!
- Rei!
- Rei...
- Rei, you're alive!
I thought you
were a goner!
Brother!
So you're finally awake.
What's this about?
I gave that man
three days to live.
What?
Valiant warriors who defy me...
I don't kill such
experts immediately.
Do you know why?
If you kill too quickly,
the fear will not spread.
But fighters
with three days to live,
will tremble in fear of death,
grieve, and suffer to the end.
Soon that terror
turns to legend.
And the name Ken-Oh
carries all the more weight.
I've hit his pressure
point, "Shinkesshu."
In three days, blood will erupt
from all over his dying body.
In the meantime,
he can taste the terror...
of death that looms
closer by the second.
Brother!
This emblem
on your shoulder!
- No!
- Mamiya!
- That's...
- It can't be!
UD! It's Yuda!
She was one of Yuda's women?
Poor thing, she must
have been through hell.
Mamiya, why is there a Yuda
emblem on your shoulder?
That man took
my future from me.
He condemned me to
fighting for the rest of my life.
This scar...
It will never go away!
Much like the
scars in my heart...
Mamiya...
Rei, don't look at me.
No!
Let's go!
This way, you have
no reason to come back here!
Rei! Hang in there!
Rei!
Ke...Ken...
Looks like the medicine
from Medicine City
isn't working too well.
You are going to defeat
Yuda, aren't you?
Yeah, I know him.
I know Yuda.
We're both men
of the South Star.
What?
He's one of the South
Star Six Sacred Fists.
There are four other masters
of the South Star Sacred Fists
besides your friend Shin and I.
Six men stand atop the 108 styles
of the South Star Sacred Fist styles.
They are known as the South
Star Six Sacred Fists.
Yuda... he's one of them.
Yuda?
I have two days left to live.
I won't seek Mamiya's love.
I only want to die for her
and live on in her heart.
In the age we live in,
the lives of men are short.
But women will have children
and pass on their tales.
The tales of brave men
and their battles!
Yuda... you're a worthy trophy
for my final moments.
I'll defeat him,
no matter what!
It's been a long time.
Mamiya.
I'm sure the scar on
your shoulder is still intact.
Yuda!
Mamiya, it seems that you too,
can see the Death Omen Star.
I hold the key
to that death.
Just like the fate of your
family rested in my hands.
Your blood will surely
make me even more beautiful.
Now, would you be so kind
to guide me to Rei?
Rei, you still haven't
rotted away?
Yuda... I'm impressed to
see you come forward.
I just came here to witness your
anaemic style first hand.
And to extinguish
the Star of Justice...
with the Star of Enchantment.
You're a sad
and pathetic fool...
devoting your final moments
to one lousy woman.
To a woman branded by me
without a tomorrow to speak of!
Is that all you
have to say?
Even if Mamiya
is destined to die...
my feelings will not change.
Mamiya... a sad woman.
At least let there be one man
willing to die just for you.
Crying over a woman?
How spineless, Rei!
Yuda... let's settle this.
South Star Crimson Crane Fist!
South Star Waterfowl Fist!
Flight of the Red Sparrow!
What gives you
so much power...
What drives me is my love
for Mamiya. It burns in my soul.
You wouldn't understand
a thing about love!
This is it for you.
Yuda, today, the Star of
Enchantment will fall to hell!
You think you've defeated me?
Fool! No one can beat me.
Not even you,
the Star of Justice!
Yuda's up to something.
Yeah... Be careful, Toki.
My star shines with
beauty and wisdom.
Do you think I came
without a plan?
What?
I can hear it now.
Soon, you'll see hell!
What the?
- What's wrong?
- What's that sound?
Look out!
What are you
trying to pull, Yuda?
Did you break the dam?
That's right!
This sandy ground will turn
to quicksand and suck people in!
Well? Now you can't move!
The South Star Waterfowl Fist's
secret techniques...
lie in intricate footwork.
Now that your lower
body is stuck in place...
you're like a waterfowl
with no wings!
You will die an ugly
death in my hands!
Rei!
The Star of Enchantment shines
more beautifully in red!
The pathetic Star of Justice
will fall in this ugly mud!
Every step that I get
closer, I'll slice you deeper!
Cut, cut, cut, cut!
Fight freely to
your heart's content.
Tell me, Rei.
Who's the strongest and the
most beautiful in this world?
I'll tell you, then.
It's me.
I, Yuda-sama, am the strongest
and the most beautiful!
Rei!
Rei, you can't lose!
Don't lose!
Rei of the Star of Justice.
You're just a pathetic clown.
You couldn't even
save one woman's life!
One more step!
One more step
and you're finished!
Rei!
The water...
The water has stopped flowing.
The Star of Deception
shines in the southern sky!
Here's the finishing strike!
South Star Crimson Crane Fist
secret technique:
Blood-Tainted Beak!
South Star Waterfowl Fist
secret technique:
Soaring White Splendor!
That's impossible!
Rei!
You can't defeat me, Yuda.
Ken!
The battle's over.
I won't die like this!
Not like this!
The man who's stronger,
more beautiful than me!
Yuda!
- Yuda-sama!
Ever since my heart
was drawn to you,
the Star of Deception has been
destined to be extinguished
by the Star of Justice.
Yuda...
Rei... you were the only man
I've ever respected.
The strongest and the most
beautiful man in the world.
At least, just let me
die in your arms.
Yuda...
Yuda!
Yuda, you too were
a lonely warrior.
But I'll be joining you soon.
Farewell, South Star
Six Sacred Fist.
The Crimson Crane Fists' Yuda,
of the Star of Deception.
Why do they have to spill
each other's blood?
Somehow, something's
gone wrong.
Mamiya.
Mami-
Rei!
Looks like my
time's finally up.
Rei.
Mamiya. Listen.
Live your life to the fullest
until the Death Omen Star falls.
Even if just for a moment,
live as a woman.
Pursue a woman's happiness!
Farewell.
Rei!
Stay back!
You must not come.
You're the last person
that I would have
witness me crumble away
and die so pathetically.
Rei!
May you be happy, Mamiya.
I've done all
that needs to be done.
I am the Star of Justice
from South Star Six Sacred Fists.
The Star of Justice lives
for others and dies for others.
I have no regrets.
Ken, Lin, Bat, Toki, Airi...
Mamiya...
Brother...
Damn it...
Rei...
Rei, I won't forget
how you lived.
Like Shin, you'll live
on in my heart.
Goodbye, Rei.
What is it, Mamiya-san?
The star...
I can't see Alcor.
The Death Omen Star
has disappeared.
Rei's love brought
us a miracle.
Rei, the Star of Justice
from South Star Six Sacred Fists.
Your legend
will live on forever.
Farewell, Rei.
PART TWO:
THE TUMULTUOUS DRAGON AND TIGER
THE
END